okay your lives your life all right
you office make sure it's shared on
there we go
alright alright people talking got like
20 people
okay so let's draft in your office and
around here in San Diego guys some stuff
to feel like putting the proper place
but operation City a fancy hide all the
secrets pretend to be working hard work
in there yeah I work in there yeah I
think yeah it's not the simulation for
Nick Castellanos well no exactly like
not yet but so gaming room we have a
game where a bunch of you are going to
be testing the code in loops
infrastructure team
down there so three people Craig Craig
is probably working on thing that we're
gonna show later
yeah she's our new power center well so
these are the research team she's
actually doing research on the videogame
sure she's probably like the best of
them actuator officer of the company we
do have promoted to officer hey sailor
oh yeah Eddie your other screen this
have two computers three monitors and
then this is all Windows right now but
if i press this hdmi switch boom Linux
and windows one Mouse one keyboard goes
back and forth shout-out to synergy
synergy don't worry cut off cut off the
words
all right so now we go to the real stuff
you can hear it key here we can you eat
so we're gonna have God we cannot focus
ID because very loud
[Music]
Pickard out here
somebody understands above I obey now
needs
siddhappa
this box is empty there if they write
one for the left one is actually to
speak they speak something
and so the eland
Rize Fox down there
so yes
there yes
some was confined in a corner
not all my parameter editor to turn of
the printer
and the thing
they're so steamy Zach
how many of us a 25
so yeah without the questions
let's see you back up to the cloud
yeah I mean like the data yes certainly
I did it out the car will be clarified
what's it all for
oh this computing it's processing it's
like mainly CPU and GPU with all the
training lock hello Cheryl how much
what's the drive size I think
what's the capacity of all the drives in
there by before one's out everything
that we're gonna stay here you know so
is the best room block has prehistoric
[Music]
okay so what can we say show off the
kitchen we didn't shut the kitchen now
there's the new kitchen
we can also talk about that coming
release of oven pilot for all the
previous users we finally found a good
way to have decent control it's not
gonna pimp on you anymore all the props
go to villain who actually is gonna use
like a completely different control sir
let's go to the IM di and some advanced
technique very better than PID it's
gonna work right
I've seen people starting to change the
EPS module please don't replace that
part of the EPS module done to the point
part that going to the PSO strongly not
recommended we came up with a good fix I
think so 5.12 you're gonna be happy with
if you have a Prius and use up a pilot
kitchen it's the new Nikola flavor
because it's Cola but without sugar or
artificial sweetener just essence it's
naturally essence and I wrote this to
work today he did I can't verify Andy do
you want to say hello disco peas just
grab the one that's just sitting there
cool any question yeah any questions off
fish anything let's see where do you
store the interns for now when I roll
thirsty space rooms yeah yeah figured
out who should be in 20 but but we do
have to garage we did show the big one
we do I like another small garage does
the new office cost more or less than
the SF house oh it costs more than I
suppose but it cost about like two times
less than the same office in the same
spot like equivalent equivalent spot in
downtown San Francisco
I mean thought bigger then then it's
it's twice the size of the of the house
who's funding all of this I mean you can
go on ranch base and see yeah yeah go
and catch these type comedy I usually
check those filings no no that's not
next model no torque issues then no
that's some different next on Honda no
no we were talking about we're talking
about the Prius
that's right drew you smile yeah we'll
come ever make their own car actually
it's a good question
so we I mean like we just we were making
fun of zoo explorer making their own car
and we had like a poster saying why we
don't make cars and showing the Zuke's
car so no we're never gonna make our own
car
where are we hiding George I don't know
are you see hiding but he's around
around is what's Greg driving Greg what
are you driving
what are you driving Greg your life you
have like how many people watch there 50
people alright what you're asking about
you this is for the simulation okay any
last questions yeah I mean I think
they're gonna do a periscope we can you
control it on the previews tomorrow I
think it's pretty good then so yeah oh
we do have hoodies somebody asked about
hoodies we do have goodies yeah we do
yeah on the shop
cool baseball caps ooh yeah yeah yeah no
it's that moment you're not the only one
Chris our three pan is needed for ct-6
they are you need three pendants yes
no mister we can open source on the
boards it's a lot of work honestly but
I'm super quiz isn't bad but if you want
to if you're an open pilot we're open
palette on the city chicks watch it
works right well you have to have access
to flex ready but it works really well
so if somebody wants to do the
experiment is doable we can open source
all day with the work that we did on the
board
mmm no office tours only periscope
office tours yeah yeah cool what can I
do if my Aeon storage is full and I
don't have access to Wi-Fi all right
CalFire off Larry but it is coming up I
go to Amber for ya it's gonna be like a
smart out of the leader that the least
like all data and allows you to keep
driving without stop logging which is I
mean it's what you wanted
it's not a hack it's Aria fix
yeah yeah that was a big problem for
quite a while plug ins versus Forbes so
lucky investor sparks what do you mean
why sure that means HD maps question
America HD maps I mean like again if not
we are using account rules that depends
on high accuracy localizations so we are
building things that depend on having an
eye accuracy like localization and
definition of cars paths in warframe so
we are using that now what what HTML are
I mean there is really no a unique
definition of them what are they like is
there a presentation of what like late
things like features like lane lines no
I don't think that's probably useful to
us what's very useful to us is
understanding in warframe what every car
has been like which is the part of each
car and yes of course we're doing that
is very useful for training our models
so what we do we do keep track awfully
nice to also train the model but we have
our own HD map so that serves the
purposes of training but our mothers
Lisbon
yeah and I mean we do an extensive using
our Ferber Street Map as well so we are
also considering like putting our own
layers in top of of a street map and I
need more features so that's like
another good way possibly of planning
defining HD maps but not the only one
yeah any plans on big model v2 yes yes I
mean the big bothered was like too big
there is definite plan for like a big
mid model meet mother is probably like
better big mother was just to be again
and it was unnecessary to be good so
Riccardo they say your voice makes me
want to buy whatever you're talking
about buy a t-shirt or a hoodie okay any
other questions before we leave anything
else you want to say Riccardo
I hope you enjoyed the new the new
office is like a bigger plane we're
gonna show you it again when everything
is like in Peten place like especially
like the hardware in the loop rome is
gonna be like a big array from literally
a closet that we have in there in the
house so there's gonna be a lot more
Young's running there and Stockholm is
gonna be clean so we're gonna show you
together yeah yeah okay all right bye
guys
all right